Amirmasoud Razavi

Islamic Azad University

📳 +98-9301041491 | 💌 amirmasoud@tutanota.com | 🧥 amirmasoud-r.github.io/Portfolio/ | 🖸 github.com/Amirmasoud-R | 🛅

linkedin.com/in/amirmasoud-razavi-a1b063338/

Personal Profile

Passionate Computer Engineering student at Islamic Azad University, Karaj Brach, with a foundation and experience in Cybersecurity. I'm interested in both offensive and defensive security. Solving the complex challenges of security problems in real-world situations piques my interest.

Education

Islamic Azad University

Karaj, Iran

B.Sc. in Computer Engineering

Feb 2024 - Graduated

• CGPA: 16.69/20

Final Project: "Purpl3 OS"

• Final Project CGPA: 20/20

· Advisor: Dr. Sasan harifi

Interests_

Reverse Engineering

Cryptography

Zero Knowledge Architecture Virtualization

Malware Analysis

Bug Bounty

GFW Censorship Bypassing

Selected Courses

Internet Engineering: 18.4/20

Operating Systems: 18/20

Fundamental of Secure Computing: 17/20

Microprocessor and Assembly Language: 18/20

Computer Programming: 17/20

Fundamental of Data Mining: 18/20

Work Experience

Teaching Assistant Karaj, Iran

TA at Islamic Azad University Karaj Brach

2023 - 2024

 I had the honor of being a TA for the Operating Systems, Operating Systems Lab and Basic Programming curriculum under the supervision of Dr. Sasan Harifi for two semesters.

ISO 27001 Specialist Jajarm, Iran

Internship at Iran Alumina

June 2023 - Jul 2023

One month mandatory internship from the university.

IT Security Tehran, Iran

Internship at Paya Net Afzar

Aug 2023 - Nov 2023

Four months of internship.

Junior Bug Bounty

Freelance Sep 2024 - Ongoing

- Javascript bug hunter.
- · OWASP Top 10.
- · API Exploitation.

Sanctuary Services

Anti GFW Censorship VPN

March 2024 - Ongoing

- · Personal entrepreneurship project.
- Sanctuary Services provides various VPN and VPS services to its users for maintaing their privacy and security at all times.
- Sacntuary VPNs bypasses all of the ultra strict GFW Censorship and DPI Limitations without affecting the user internet quality.
- · Sanctuary Services has zero log policy and does not tolerate any form of privacy violation of its users.
- Due to the privacy focused nature of the service, by hosting its own DNS any form of unwanted tracking, advertisement, scam domains, malware honey pots and etc. is eliminated.

Projects and Research Experience

A Giza Pyramids Construction metaheuristic approach based on upper bound calculation for solving the network reliability problem

December 2024

Elsevier, Applied Soft Computing Volume 167, Part A.

- https://doi.org/10.1016/j.asoc.2024.112241
- Technical Skills: Matlab, Computer Networks, Researching.
- Soft Skills: Teamwork, Leadership, Passion, Dedication

Purpl3 OS 2023

Final Project of BSc

- A lightweight yet modern Linux Distro based on Debian/Ubuntu.
- Designed and optimized for the extremely outdated lab computers of Azad University Karaj Brach.
- Runs just under 400 Mb of RAM and at 1 Core of CPU.
- Optimization of CPU Governance, I/O, Boot-loader, Kernel, Background Services.
- · With modern and custom GUI with up to date kernel, Capable of running the newest packages with ease
- Technical Skills: Linux, Computer Networks, Bash, C, C++.
- Soft Skills: Curiosity, Passion

Anti GFW VPN March 2024

Personal Project

- Successfully developed a VPN to bypass the GFW
- · Utilizes various methods and techniques in order to mask the users connection as if it is a simple http traffic visiting a webpage.
- · Very light weight with little overhead.
- Completely encrypted to ensure user safety.
- Technical Skills: Linux, Computer Networks, Python, C++.
- · Soft Skills: Curiosity, Dedication, Researching

Privacy Goggles Ongoing

An ongoing project

- A project with the sole purpose of protection against unauthorized ai surveillance
- Disguised as a stylish sunglasses protecting both your eyes and your privacy by disrupting the ability of computer vision and facial recognition algorithms
- Technical Skills: C, CodeVisionAVR, Proteus, Microprocessor Hardware, Electronic Hardware
- · Soft Skills: Critical Thinking.

Simple SSH Cracker 2024

Personal Project

- Simple educational SSH cracker to understand the procedure and how to encounter it
- Technical Skills: C++, Linux, Scripting.
- Soft Skills: Curiosity

Skills

Programming

Python ● ● ● ● , CSS/HTML ● ● ● ● , JavaScript ● ● ● ● , SQL ● ● ● ● , and C++ ● ● ● ●.

Also familiar with Matlab.

Miscellaneous

Computer Networks ● ● ● ● , Linux ● ● ● ● , Wireshark ● ● ● ● , Burp Suite ● ● ● ● ,

Metasploit ● ● ● ● , Git ● ● ● ● , and LaTeX ● ● ● ●

Soft Skills Teamwork, Leadership, Presentation Skills, Mentoring, Reliability, Brainstorming, Curiosity, Problem Solving, and Public Speaking.

Achievements

2023 Best Project Award, Islamic Azad University Karaj Brach, Fall Semester
 Ongoing Nominated Best Research Award, Islamic Azad University Karaj Brach

Interests

Researching I love Researching about Politics, Social Studies, Religion and anything related to Privacy or Cybersecurity

Cooking As an avid foodie I really enjoy cooking and baking different recipes from from various cuisines

Video Games

At the end of the day the only thing that could make me relaxed is playing video games and socializing with my friends

from all over the world.

Exercising Whether if its hiking in the mountains or boxing in the ring, I enjoy most forms of exerciser and working out

Languages

English Professional proficiency - IELTS: 7.5/9

Persian Native proficiency

Refrences

Sassan Harifi Assistant Professor s.harifi@kiau.ac.ir

Amineh Amini Assistant Professor amini.kiau@gmail.com